https://www.terason.com/privacy/

Click Here For Technical Support
AboutHistoryTestimonialsNewsManagement TeamCareersThe ProductsuSmart 3300 NexGenuSmart 3300 NexGen CartuSmart 3200T NexGenuSmart 3200T NexGen Cartt3200t3200 CartAccessoriesThe TechnologyCapacitive Touch ScreenDynamic Depth Resolution (DDRTM)Enhanced Needle Visualization (ENV)Hybrid Hard DriveImage QualityOmniBeamOpen ArchitectureSmart Console DesignSmart GesturesTMSmart MarkTMSmart Resolution ImagingSmart TrainingTMSolid State Drive (SSD)TeraVisionTMIITeraScapeTMuConnect®The CompanyEducational ProgramsFAQsProduct LiteratureSociety Meetings and Conferences 2020Partners CoursesContactDirectionsRequest InformationGet a QuoteDistributors and PartnersBlog
Privacy
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT CAREFULLY.
Privacy is very important to us. We also understand that privacy is very important to you. This Privacy Statement tells you how we protect and use information that we gather through this Teratech website. This website and this Privacy Statement are intended for a U.S. audience.
We may change this Privacy Statement at any time and for any reason. Significant changes to the Privacy Statement are discussed below in the Section called “Changes to the Privacy Statement.” We encourage you to review this Privacy Statement each time you visit the website.
By using this website, you agree to the terms of the most recent version of this Privacy Statement. Please read our Terms of Use to understand the general rules about your use of this website. Except as written in any other disclaimers, policies, terms of use, or other notices on this website, this Privacy Statement and the Terms of Use are the complete agreement between you and Teratech with respect to your use of this website. You may be subject to additional terms that may apply when you access particular services or materials on certain areas in this website, or by following a link from this website.
What information do we gather?
Introduction
The information we receive, and how we use it, depends on what you do when visiting our website. We collect and use your non-personal information (information that is not identifiable to you personally) differently than your personal information.
What Is non-personal information?
Non-personal information is information we collect through this website that does not identify you as an individual person. It may include information such as the following:
• the type of web browser software you use
(for example, Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer)
• the name of the domain from which you access the Internet
• the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our website
• the date and time you access our website
• which pages you have visited on our website
• personal information that has been de-identified
If you visit our website to read or download information, such as information about a health condition or about one of our products, we may collect certain non-personal information about you from your computer. This information is collected from your computer’s web browser: If you
only read or download information on our website, we do not collect or learn your name, email address, home address, or other personal information about you. We may place a text file called a cookie in the browser files of your computer when you visit. The cookie may be stored on your computer’s hard drive. The information that we collect using cookies is non-personal information. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our website may not work properly for you if you do so. We will not allow third parties to place cookies on our website.
What does Teratech do with non-personal information?
Because non-personal information cannot identify you or be tied to you in any way, there are no restrictions on the ways that we can use or share non-personal information. We are always looking for ways to better serve you and improve this website. We will use non-personal information from you to help us make this website more useful to visitors. We also will use non-personal information for other business purposes. For example, we may use non-personal information or aggregate de-identified personal information to:
• create reports for internal use to develop programs, products, services or content
• customize the information or services that are of interest to you
• share it with or sell it to third parties
• provide aggregated “traffic statistics” and “response rates” to third parties
What Is personal information?
Personal information is information we collect through this website that we can use to specifically identify you, such as your:
• name
• address
• telephone number
• email address
In some places on this website you have the opportunity to send us personal information about yourself. For example, you may fill out a registration form, a survey, or an email form.
You also may choose to allow us to personalize your visits to the website, in which case we will ask you for certain personal information to make your visits to our website more helpful to you. When this information is combined with the non-personal information that we collect through
cookies (described above), we will be able to tell that you have visited our website before and can personalize your access to our website, for example, by telling you about new features that may be of interest to you.
How does Teratech keep and use personal information?
We may keep and use personal information we collect from you through this website to provide you with access to this website. In addition, we may keep and use your personal information:
• to respond to your requests
• to personalize your access to our website, for example, by telling you about new features that may be of interest to you
• to develop records, including records of your personal information
• to contact you with information that might be of interest to you, including information about clinical trials and about products and services of ours and of others
• for analytical purposes and to research, develop and improve programs, products, services and content
• to remove your personal identifiers (your name, email address, etc). In this case, you would no longer be identified as a single unique individual. Once we have de-identified information, it is non-personal information and we may treat it like other non-personal information.
• to enforce this Privacy Statement and other rules about your use of this website
• to protect our rights or property
• to protect someone’s health, safety or welfare
• to comply with a law or regulation, court order or other legal process
Does Teratech ever share personal information with third parties?
Teratech will not share your personal information collected from this website with an unrelated third party without your permission, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Statement.
In the ordinary course of business, we will share some personal information with companies that we hire to perform services or functions on our behalf. For example, we may use different vendors or suppliers to ship you products that you order on our website. In these cases, we provide the
vendor with information to process your order such as your name and mailing address. In all cases in which we share your personal information with a third party, we will not authorize them to keep, disclose or use your information with others except for the purpose of providing the services we asked them to provide.
We will not sell, exchange or publish your personal information, except in conjunction with a corporate sale, merger, dissolution, or acquisition.
We may be legally compelled to release your personal information in response to a court order, subpoena, search warrant, law or regulation. We may cooperate with law enforcement authorities in investigating and prosecuting website visitors who violate our rules or engage in behavior which
is harmful to other visitors (or illegal). We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we feel that the disclosure is necessary to:
• enforce this Privacy Statement and the other rules about your use of this website
• protect our rights or property
• protect someone’s health, safety or welfare
• comply with a law or regulation, court order or other legal process
Please note: In addition to the ways that we may keep, disclose, and use information described in this Privacy Statement, we also may keep, disclose, and use personally identifiable information that you give us through this website in ways that we believe are consistent with FDA and other
governmental guidance, directions, regulations, and laws.
What about privacy on other websites?
This website may contain links to other websites. Some of those websites may be operated by Teratech, and some may be operated by third parties. We provide the links for your convenience, but we do not review, control, or monitor the privacy practices of websites operated by others. This Privacy Statement does not apply to any other website, even the other Teratech websites. We are not responsible for the performance of websites operated by third parties or for your business dealings with them. Therefore, whenever you leave this website we recommend that you review each website’s privacy practices and make your own conclusions regarding the adequacy of these practices.
Does Teratech ever communicate directly with visitors to this website?
We may contact you periodically by email, mail or telephone to provide information regarding programs, products, services and content that may be of interest to you. In addition, some of the features on this website allow you to communicate with us using an online form. If your
communication requests a response from us, we will send you a response via email. The email response or confirmation may include your personal information, including personal information about your health, your name, address, etc. We cannot guarantee that our emails to you will be
secure from unauthorized interception.
Are there special rules about children’s privacy?
We care about protecting the online privacy of children. We will not intentionally collect any personal information (such as a child’s name or email address) from children under the age of 13. If you think that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, please
contact us.
What about website security?
We take reasonable steps to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. In particular, email sent to or from this site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email
How to contact Teratech.
If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Statement, please use the Contact feature or contact us at:
Teratech Corporation
77 Terrace Hall Ave.
Burlington, MA 01803
781.270.4143
TERASON INTRANET LOGINSitemapHome
AnesthesiaBreastCardiologyCritical CareEmergency MedicineEMSEndocrinologyMilitaryMobileMusculoskeletalOB/GYNPhlebologyPICC LineRadiology/IRVascular
CareersNewsVideoMSK
TerasonTerason Intranet LoginMSK UltrasmartSitemapHomeRegulatory/ComplianceUser GuidesPrivacyTerms of Use
AboutHistoryTestimonialsNewsManagement TeamCareersThe ProductsuSmart 3300 NexGenuSmart 3300 NexGen CartuSmart 3200T NexGenuSmart 3200T NexGen Cartt3200t3200 CartAccessoriesThe TechnologyCapacitive Touch ScreenDynamic Depth Resolution (DDRTM)Enhanced Needle Visualization (ENV)Hybrid Hard DriveImage QualityOmniBeamOpen ArchitectureSmart Console DesignSmart GesturesTMSmart MarkTMSmart Resolution ImagingSmart TrainingTMSolid State Drive (SSD)TeraVisionTMIITeraScapeTMuConnect®The CompanyEducational ProgramsFAQsProduct LiteratureSociety Meetings and Conferences 2020Partners CoursesContactDirectionsRequest InformationGet a QuoteDistributors and PartnersBlog
